The Judge from Hell
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN SAFE SITUATIONS
Defendant,
your final statement, please.
I know I won't see her again,
but I want to say
that I really loved Minjeong.
The defendant is hereby ordered
to pay a fine of three million won.
Thank you, Your Honor. Thank you!
Please, let me go.
I'll be back. Stay pretty.
She's dead.
EPISODE 2
Shall we go talk somewhere quiet?
What would we have to talk about?
Come on. It won't be long.
Okay.
What brings you here, Detective?
- You know why.
- I don't.
I told you clearly
to stay away from Cha Minjeong.
Actually...
Mom left when I was in high school.
Dad kicked me out when he remarried.
It's because I grew up without parents.
Shut up!
Not every orphan is like you.
So are you going to hit me?
That won't do you good.
Yeah. I'll beat you to a pulp
and resign.
It will really be
abuse of authority this time.
Let go.
Daon! Stop!
Aren't you Judge Kang?
- We meet again.
- Right.
- Do we arrest him without a warrant?
- He has to come on his own.
Will you come with us
on suspicion of stalking Ms. Cha?
You may refuse
and can leave during the transfer.
You also have the right to an attorney.
What'll it be? Clock's ticking.
I'll go.
- Let's go.
- Where?
Can you get rid of that?
I thought you didn't believe in God.
But you have a cross in your car?
You don't believe in God
but want to go to Heaven?
Is that it?
I don't want to go to Heaven.
You mean you can't.
People who raise their fists first
go to Hell.
And your car is weird like you.
Why were you at Moon Jeongjun's place?
To monitor him.
To make sure the person I released
is being good.
It's like a follow-up service.
- But where are we going?
- To do some follow-up service.
Please, let me go.
But can I kill
your parents instead?
I just asked you a question.
LOVE YOU TO DEATH
MINE FOREVER!
How pretty.
I'll be back. Stay pretty.
See the results of your ruling?
Are you sorry now?
Not at all.
Had you not released him with just a fine,
she wouldn't have been attacked.
What if I gave him one year?
This wouldn't have happened in a year?
At the very least,
the victim and her family
wouldn't have felt that
the law had abandoned them.
Your ruling was a secondary offense.
I merely made a ruling based on the law.
Stop pestering a blameless person
and resent the laws instead.
But it's you who ruled based on that law.
Countless people have lost their lives
from cases like this.
They appear in the news
and the public is outraged.
I'm talking about terrible crimes
and lenient punishments.
And everyone forgets about the dead.
And when someone dies again,
it starts all over again.
Is that my fault?
We'll apply for
an arrest warrant for Moon Jeongjun.
Is an arrest investigation necessary?
A few visits to the station
should suffice.
That's up to me, the detective, to decide.
He won't be released so easily this time.
Because not all judges will be like you.
You broke into
Ms. Cha's place, right?
No. Minjeong opened the door.
She asked you to come in?
Yes.
And you admit to assaulting Ms. Cha?
Do I have to answer this
when I'm here voluntarily?
Why did you bring this?
In case Minjeong needed something
to nail while I was gone.
After you left,
Minjeong hung herself in the living room.
Is she dead? No, right?
Didn't you want her dead?
What happened to Minjeong?
She's alive.
Please be understanding.
Excuse me.
I'm opening it. One, two...
Ms. Cha! Ms. Cha!
Ms. Cha, you can't do this!
Cut her down! Hurry!
Minjeong! Ah!
Oh, my God!
We told you
to come home with us.
Why didn't you listen to me?
Mom.
I'm sorry.
But can you please let me go?
I don't want to live anymore.
That's a relief.
I can't live without her.
She tried to die because of you.
She's a bit overdramatic.
And every couple fights.
Why must the state
intervene in our lovers' quarrel?
Fine. When you're in court,
repeat that nonsense.
That dating abuse
is just a lovers' quarrel.
It's been six hours now. Can I go?
- Park Donghun.
- Yes?
Get an arrest warrant.
Provisional measures, too.
Yes, ma'am.
Is an arrest investigation possible?
He almost killed her.
What kind of judge wouldn't approve it?
What the hell
is that bastard looking at?
I should rip his eyes out.
I'll get him.
Hey. Come here.
Damn it!
We should have
kept a closer eye on her place.
That was my misjudgment.
You did your best.
Eunseop's right.
He's the bad guy.
- Han Daon.
- Yes?
Don't let him out of your sight.
Yes, ma'am.
- Here.
- Yeah.
BABE, ARE YOU OKAY? I'M SO...
Come on. I'll take you home.
I'm fine.
I'm not.
Just come.
Darn it. He catches on quick.
Hey, Moon Jeongjun.
I'm going to sleep
in front of your house every night.
Don't even think about leaving.
This number is...
She's not home and won't pick up.
Where is she?
Jus... I mean, Judge Kang.
What happened?
You look terrible.
What happened last night?
Did you take care of it?
Does it look like I did? Does it?
Judge Kang.
Ah. That shower felt so good.
Here.
- Seriously?
- Right.
Here.
But what happened?
You didn't leave her to die, did you?
- She's alive.
- What?
Then...
It's over for this case, right?
Having a pulse doesn't mean she's alive.
Her mental state's all messed up,
and she has no will to live.
Breathing isn't living.
Still, a doctor has to determine her death
for her to be dead.
Are we defining life or death
by human standards?
Then why am I here?
Right. You're right.
Still, Moon Jeongjun
didn't kill her himself...
Mental murder is also murder.
Yes, you're right.
But Han Daon's the bigger problem.
I feel like he keeps getting in my way.
Just get rid of him, then.
Don't you know
I can only send those who've killed?
Justitia, go to the human world,
punish ten murderers who are unrepentant
and unforgiven,
take their lives, and send them to Hell.
You have one year.
Just leave Han Daon alone.
He is a pain in the butt,
but the way he challenges me
is kind of adorable.
Adorable? Justitia, don't tell me...
- No. So shut up.
- Yes.
Either way, this case is a fail, right?
If the arrest warrant is rejected,
maybe not.
Come on. You think
there's another terrible judge like you?
You really think there isn't?
Detective Kim,
the arrest warrant's been rejected.
What? Rejected?
- Yes.
- What's the reason?
He agreed to come in and cooperated.
He's not a flight risk.
Seriously?
What the hell is this crap?
If it were that judge's daughter,
this wouldn't happen.
Daon, go watch over
Ms. Cha and her family.
Yes, ma'am.
JUDGE KANG BITNA
Can you see me?
Yes, I can see you.
We checked the cameras
at Ms. Cha's apartment.
Insulation tape was stuck
on the outer lens, making it not visible.
I'll be in the area at night
for the time being.
If anyone comes by, don't let them in,
and give me a call.
I'll leave once I make sure
you've locked the door.
Okay, thank you.
Goodbye.
It's Detective Han Daon.
What is it, Minjeong?
I couldn't see then too.
And he said he was an officer.
It's him!
He's here to kill you guys!
It's all right.
Honey, call the detective now!
Why aren't you calling him?
If I do,
we'll be safe for today.
But even if he gets a prison sentence,
he'll be back out again.
How long do you think
the police can protect us?
- Mom, untie me.
- No.
Dad, I'll go take care of it.
I'll go out.
Untie me!
Minjeong, look at me!
What did I say when I brought you home?
I promised I'd protect you
no matter what, didn't I?
No one can protect me, Dad.
Honey! Take her to the bedroom
and lock the door.
And don't come out
no matter what you hear.
Once it quiets down,
call the police. Okay?
- Hurry, go!
- No.
- Get inside.
- Dad!
- Come here.
- Let go!
- Minjeong, get in!
- Minjeong, please!
- No, Dad!
- Get in!
- Dad!
No!
Sir, calm down.
I'm sorry, Detective.
This is a smart watch.
You can each wear one.
When you press the SOS button...
It's my fault.
Mom and Dad almost died because of me.
It's not your fault.
But everyone says it's my fault.
That I have terrible taste in men.
That I dated the wrong guy
and I don't even know
how to end the relationship.
All this won't work.
It ends only when I'm dead.
Excuse me for a moment.
Yeah, what is it?
Daon, Moon Jeongjun's dead.
What?
The Judge from Hell
Justitia,
did something good happen?
You're glowing today.
Yes, the trial ended very well.
JUDGE'S OFFICE
- From the day before yesterday.
- What should I have for lunch?
12 HOURS AGO
Jeongjun, it's me, Minjeong.
Meet me at 323-21 in Hwangcheon-dong
at midnight tonight.
You want to talk in person?
It's too late.
I'm going to kill your parents first.
If you keep this up,
I'm calling the police.
The police? Go ahead.
What's a few months in prison?
Don't be like that. Let's meet.
I'm the one you want anyways.
Hey.
I know you're plotting with the police
to lure me out there.
I'm not.
Then get down here now.
I can't. My parents are still up.
And the police are watching.
See you there at midnight.
We'll talk then.
THE GREATCOAT
GIACOMO PUCCINI
CONGRATULATIONS
ON THE REDEVELOPMENT PROJECT
DEMOLISH
Minjeong, let's play
Judge Kang?
What are you doing here?
What do you think?
I'm here to kill you.
What?
Where are you hiding? Get out now.
Gosh. I'm so tired.
Seriously?
Can I go home now?
Yes.
Good work today.
I had to work late...
because of you.
Your real trial starts now.
Do you admit that you, sinner
Moon Jeongjun, murdered Cha Minjeong
and yet are unrepentant and unforgiven?
Minjeong's not dead.
And Minjeong's already forgiven me.
I'll be the one to judge
if she's dead, if she's forgiven you,
and if you really are repentant.
Let me ask you again.
Do you admit to your crimes?
You gave me the fine.
It's all over now. Why are you doing this?
I told you.
This is your real trial.
I've never killed anyone.
I'm going to report you
for attempted murder.
What the hell?
Welcome to my world.
You are about to be
on the receiving end of what you've done.
That's the rule in Hell. Understood?
Yes.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kang Bitna.
Wow, I'm full.
Already?
Have more, babe.
I'm full. I'm done.
- Are you ignoring me right now?
- What?
No, I'm not...
I said eat.
Eat.
Eat. I said eat.
Are you crazy?
Why aren't you doing what I say?
Sorry, I won't do it again.
You know I can't live without you, right?
I'd rather die than break up with you.
I'll kill myself.
Hey, stop it!
Just put it down first!
Don't ever ask to break up again.
I can't live without you, okay?
Hmm?
Let's break up.
Break up?
So, is this...
a goodbye party?
What you did that day,
it's too creepy.
Let's end this.
I was trying to be nice until now!
I told you
not to ask to break up ever again.
For God's sake.
I kept this here just in case.
I'm finally using it.
Who are you? Why are you doing this?
Stop.
Stop?
This is only the beginning.
I think I'm going to die.
Please hurry up.
- Honey, open the door.
- Please come quick!
Open the door.
Honey, stay well until we meet again.
Hey...
You're home.
I've been released.
Why didn't you tell me you moved?
How did you find me?
How did you even get in?
If you press that,
I'll end up back in prison.
It'll probably be a year this time.
But you know what?
Next time I come back out again...
I'm going to kill you.
Come in.
Hurry.
I'm making braised tofu
to celebrate my release. Oh, wait.
For betraying me and calling the police.
Oh, my.
You're hair's so long now, babe.
I learned how to cut hair inside.
I'll cut you after we eat.
I mean, your hair.
I won't...
call the police.
I'll give you whatever you want.
Money or anything.
So please, let's break up.
I told you not to ask me that.
All I want is you.
But why do you keep asking to break up?
I told you not to ask me
to break up again.
Why do you keep ignoring me?
- Why won't you do what I say?
- Why?
Please just let me go. I'm begging you.
Fine. I'll let you go.
Go.
You'll never be free of me.
Until you die.
I love you, babe.
Oh, my. I'm sorry.
Babe, are you okay? Does it hurt a lot?
So why didn't you just listen to me?
Sorry, I made a mistake.
Babe, where are you going?
Oh, no.
It must have hurt so bad.
Babe, open the door.
The longer you take,
the worse it'll be for you.
Babe.
No.
Open up before I get the bat again.
Babe.
Open the door now. Come on.
Do you really think you can escape me?
You're mine forever.
I love you to death.
Don't feel good?
I feel nauseous, too. But I had no choice.
This is part of the trial.
Those who do not admit their crimes,
shall feel the same pain
experienced by the victim and more
before the trial can resume again.
Hell?
I'm here to take care of guys like you.
A demon from Hell.
So,
a crazy demon from Hell is here
to seek revenge for Minjeong?
Wrong. I don't do anything for humans.
I only take care of
disgusting murderers like you.
- Minjeong's still alive.
- No.
The night you trampled on her soul,
she was already dead.
That's ridiculous.
I told you before.
I'm the judge who decides
what's ridiculous or not.
Gosh, I'm being too nice today.
Shall I make a judgement now?
I was wrong, Your Honor.
Please forgive me this once.
I just don't get it.
Why do humans ask judges
to forgive them for crimes
they've inflicted on others?
Please, let me go.
Mmm...
Yeah, I'm still in trial.
Is the clean-up crew on standby?
They know the address?
Don't do something you'll regret.
You'll be the one
to regret, you bitch!
Die! Die.
I'm going to kill you
and Minjeong and her parents. All of them.
So die!
Die!
Having fun?
- I couldn't control my strength.
- Sorry.
From now on,
I'm going to hit you the human way.
Let go!
How fun. Go for it again.
Die!
I hit you only
a fraction of how much you hit her.
But you're down already?
Get up.
Please, stop.
Cha Minjeong asked you the same thing.
"Please, stop."
Please forgive me this once.
Don't you pity me?
I was wrong, Your Honor.
You were?
Yes.
Do you admit
Cha Minjeong is dead because of you?
Yes.
If not for me,
she wouldn't have tried to kill herself.
But you know
she hasn't forgiven you, right?
Of course. I wouldn't forgive me either.
Are you really remorseful?
Yes, I really am.
Mmm.
And you admit you deserve
to die?
Yes, I deserve to die.
Then die.
Go to Hell.
Gehenna!
Court is adjourned.
Isn't that just harassment?
You're here.
Hey.
Really? That's gross.
What's that on his forehead?
Looks like he was killed inside
and dragged out here.
You're right.
Why would they leave the body
where everyone can see it?
Maybe they wanted
to dump it somewhere far but gave up
or to display the brutality.
There are no bloodstains from here.
Way too clean, right?
Yes.
Doesn't seem like a murder scene.
Of course, it's clean.
They've been cleaning forever.
They're complete professionals.
Are they that good?
Of course. They're the go-to guys
in Seoul and Gyeonggi regions.
Anyway, they've got
a good reputation in Hell.
- But why haven't I heard of them?
- What?
Well, you don't really
care about underlings.
They're at the bottom
of the chain in Hell.
I'm an egalitarian, okay?
You have a tendency to overstate my evil.
I'm not overstating, it's a fact...
I mean...
Take it.
Justitia,
the police will be scratching their heads
thanks to these guys.
SERGEANT CLEANING
I'll clean the traces
of Justitia still left on the body.
This area is
completely destroyed, too.
Oh, right.
You know,
when I told them that you ordered the job,
they said they were completely honored.
And promised to be
extra meticulous.
Mmm. Let's go.
Get every crack and crevice today.
Justitia is a total pain.
If we make a mistake,
she'll have our heads.
I heard she's a complete nutjob.
But we can clean up the body for her.
Why did she ask us
to drag it out to the front door?
- Because she's a pain.
- Is she sick?
I wanted to show them
what happens to bad guys.
But the police will see it, too.
Hmm. Yeah, I wanted them to.
Watching them muddle about,
unable to find any clues...
It's fun.
Darn it.
It's dangerous.
It doesn't all fit!
You'll break the car!
The National Forensic Service
sent Moon Jeongjun's autopsy report.
There are multiple fractures,
but the cause of death is heavy bleeding.
The stab to his abdomen.
Where was Moon Jeongjun last seen?
By the entrance
of Ms. Cha's apartment complex.
He was caught on camera
talking on the phone with someone.
Three hours later, he got off a taxi
at Nobong intersection.
And then he was seen
walking towards Hwangcheon-dong.
I got his messaging history
and call logs from that time.
The last person he was in contact with
was using a burner phone.
Were there any people or cars
that approached there around that time?
That neighborhood is a redevelopment site,
so there are no cameras.
There's no one else
besides the villa residents.
WHO SPOKE WITH HIM LAST?
They were determined.
Request search dog assistance.
- Check all the empty homes.
- Yes.
- Yes, ma'am.
And did you look into the scar
left on Moon's forehead?
Yes. It's here.
I can't get used to that.
Flip the photo left and right.
It means "Hell" in ancient Greek.
In Latin,
there's a letter "H" in the middle.
- So it's read, "Gehenna."
- Gehenna? Wow.
Wow. Who on earth
kills someone and brands them
with the word "Hell"?
Gehenna...
Hell.
It's a lot, right?
I can see why judges die from overwork.
To kill just one person,
I read all those case files all night.
But I still have nine left.
Justitia, I...
I thought about it.
We can select bad guys through trials
because this is a criminal court.
But...
there's another place
teeming with bad guys as much as here.
The police station?
Become a policewoman?
No, you don't have to
become a police officer.
You can also do it
through a policeman you know.
That man Han Daon who you said was cute?
He won't tell me anything.
He doesn't like me.
Well, obviously.
He'd have to be crazy to like you.
Or...
Well...
So, what I'm saying is,
maybe you can try
getting on the detective's good side.
Forget it.
I can find it myself.
- Yes?
- The chief judge asked for you.
He's really mad. I wonder what it is.
What could I have done to make him...
Huh. She's so rude.
But what's up with that guy?
Find something.
I, who you'd have to be crazy to like,
am leaving.
CHIEF JUDGE'S OFFICE
Judge Kang.
Moon Jeongjun.
How could you release him
with a mere fine?
At the very least
It should've been based on common sense.
Since when have judges
judged with their common sense?
What?
Are you going to take responsibility
if the defendant retaliates
against the victim?
What if I do?
Judge Kang, I know
it was a traumatic accident.
And that you're like this because of it.
But if you keep causing trouble like this,
there's only so much
I can cover up for you.
If you're a judge,
you should act like one.
And not only in trials...
Those loud outfits
and that disheveled hair.
And your makeup. Change it.
Understand what I'm saying?
But I'm dressed very elegantly.
Only respond with "Yes" or "No"!
No!
Gosh, my head.
Am I unwell?
If not for Assemblyman Jeong,
I'd banish her to the countryside.
ASSEMBLYMAN JEONG JAEGEOL
Oh, no. It's Assemblyman Jeong.
I heard you got an earful from the chief.
Is it just me,
or do you seem really happy about that?
Or course, I'm not happy.
You were in there for only ten minutes.
He let you off easy.
Who is this Assemblyman Jeong?
Is he my sponsor or something?
There he is.
Volunteered serving
free meals at a homeless shelter.
To help them rejoin society,
Assemblyman Jeong...
I don't know who that is.
Seriously? You don't remember
Assemblyman Jeong?
You can forget your parents,
but you should remember him.
You don't remember
breaking off the engagement?
Oh, my.
I broke off the engagement
with this Assemblyman Jeong?
Not with him. With his son.
His oldest son, I think.
Of course he was the oldest son.
His second son is a scumbag.
I guess I've been
too indifferent to myself.
Seonho, you look good.
Yes, I probably do.
I'm off drugs now.
Seonho.
How is Judge Kang doing?
She's your ex-fiance. Why haven't you
checked in on her at all?
Well...
I'm sure he's busy with work.
He doesn't have time.
I hear you're really busy with
the redevelopment of Hwangcheon-dong.
I saw it on the news.
I heard Judge Kang lost her memories
because of the incident.
Apparently, she's lost
most of her memories.
She's a different person now.
Please watch over her.
Of course. I've been
watching over her closely
like a mother hen looking after her eggs.
You should make the time
to ask after her yourself.
I will.
NO TO REDEVELOPMENT
WITHOUT RESIDENT CONSENT!
Should I drive if you're tired?
I have too much left to pay
in installments to let you drive it.
Then step on it more.
If you were going to drive this slow,
why buy a sports car?
You have to drive slow in alleys.
Don't you know?
But why is this neighborhood so dark?
I hope that's all it is.
There are no cameras here,
so it's a scary neighborhood.
That's how I was able to send one.
I know it's going to be redeveloped,
but it's too run-down.
If only someone hadn't spent
all her salary
and racked up credit card debt
to shop at high-end brands...
Keep talking, and I'll redevelop
that mouth of yours.
Why do humans think
being a judge is so great?
They work overtime every day
and still get criticized.
You wouldn't if you judged properly.
Thy mercy is even greater
Than life itself
HWANGCHEON VILLA
Oh, my. Shalom!
Damn it.
Shalom.
Shalo...
Going to church again tonight?
No, I'm picking up the elderly
from this apartment.
Oh, right.
Today's the neighborhood meeting.
Yes, but I won't be there.
What?
But there'll be snacks.
Do you think I'm the kind of person
you can win over with snacks?
Yes.
Start talking so we can go.
I have to go collect the recycling.
Gosh, what's the hurry?
All right.
I called an urgent meeting today
because...
Here. You can write down
your names and sign here.
- Here.
- Let me see.
This is a petition
against the redevelopment.
We all talk a lot about redevelopment,
but that's not...
You should stay longer.
You'll drone on and tell us to believe
in Jesus so we can go to Heaven.
Why would I?
Drone on?
You should take
the side dishes I made there.
Goodness.
You should all sign, too.
At first, my friends all signed yes
thinking it would be a good thing.
They left and lived elsewhere
for a few years.
And when they came in,
they asked for a lot of money.
Who is this redevelopment for?
We should really think about this.
And when they moved, things like sofas...
I'll defer for now.
I can't just sign anything
and regret it later.
Half off your rent
and no more maintenance fees.
That won't be enough to convince her.
KANG BITNA
Good.
We're now all in the same boat.
- Goodbye, then.
- What?
Where are you going?
Let's pray before you leave. Okay?
Lord, there's a woman
in her 30s who's lost her way.
Please keep our unit 201
as far away from Satan as possible.
And pave the road to Heaven...
I got a reply.
- Already?
- Yes.
Lord told me...
to go home and sleep.
Come to church with me next week...
That was exhausting.
Why does the landlady
have to be a church deaconess?
I have to kill
the remaining nine and go back.
Extract information using Detective Han?
With what? How?
Like that?
You're a genius.
Minjeong.
TOP-NOTCH NOBONG POLICE
How are you feeling?
I'm a lot better.
And I'll come back to my work.
That's great.
It's all thanks to you.
Actually...
Judge Kang Bitna came
to see me a few days ago.
Why?
Crying again?
What are you wishing for today?
And did what you wished for last time
come true?
What did you ask for?
To save them.
My death was inevitable.
So I asked Him to leave me to die
and save my innocent parents instead.
I told you.
He doesn't really grant wishes.
And He didn't.
You and your parents are all alive.
You didn't hear
I almost died because of you?
Sounds like you want me to apologize.
Sorry, I'm not at all apologetic.
Why did you come to see me?
The joy you feel
because Moon Jeongjun is dead
is only natural because you're human.
I came to tell you there's
no need to feel guilty about it.
But if you still feel bad,
confess everything to Him.
He's stingy about granting wishes.
But I heard He's generous
to those who tell Him their sins honestly.
We won't be seeing each other again.
Be well.
I still resent her.
But when she said
I didn't have to feel guilty,
it comforted me more than anything else.
Actually, that day...
I was praying for repentance.
Dear Lord.
I know it's terrible of me
to be glad about someone's death.
But I have been freed from the fear
that he'll come after me again
and the terror
that he might murder my family.
I'm completely free.
I wanted to give everything up
and take my life.
But I want to live again now.
I'm a terrible person, right?
What the...
What are you doing? That was dangerous.
Nothing happened. Calm down.
What are you doing here?
How did you know where I was?
Why am I here?
You blocked my number
and ignored my calls, so I'm here to talk.
How did I know where you were?
A detective from the station told me.
He spoke in a dialect.
He just told you I was here?
I said I was your girlfriend
and that I wanted to surprise you.
He said, "Daon is finally dating someone!"
He shouted a lot.
He gave me this address right away.
Why would you lie like that?
If you don't like that I lied, let's date.
Then it won't be a lie.
I care more about personality.
Mmm. Then I'm your perfect gal.
Let's talk over
some grilled pork and soju.
I don't want to talk to you.
This isn't just any pork.
It's deep scored.
And domestic, not imported.
You can have it all.
Really? Then that leaves me no choice.
I'll share it with the other officers
at the station tomorrow.
And I'll tell them all about just how much
we love each other!
Oh!
Gosh, it's heavy.
Thank you.
Ah.
Judges are buried in records,
unaware of what's happening on site.
But I realized watching you
that the discouragement you feel when
a hard-to-catch criminal gets off too easy
must be really great.
So I wanted to treat you to dinner.
It's not cooked yet.
Yes, it's rare.
- Give it.
- Sheesh.
I heard you went to see Cha Minjeong.
She told you already?
She must have really bad-mouthed me.
She said you comforted her.
I never did that.
I'm more curious
about what you think of me.
At first, I was grateful.
Then you were cool.
After the trial...
I'm sure you despised me. I know.
Then what about now?
I'm confused.
It's hard being
a violent crimes detective, isn't it?
Nothing in this world is easy.
Are there any cases
you just can't break these days?
Like maybe there's a brutal killer?
Like someone who caused someone's death
even if they didn't really kill.
- Cases like that?
- A lot.
Oh...
And among those, are any still uncaught?
Hmm...
- It's confidential.
- I won't tell anyone.
I don't have friends to tell anyways.
Makes sense that you don't have friends.
Still, no.
Fine.
Let's drink for now.
So, if there's a murderer you still
haven't caught, tell me their name.
I don't need many. Just nine.
Or even just one.
I'm just curious, please?
Hmm...
Fine. But...
you can't tell anyone.
Understood.
What are their names?
Han Daon.
I already know your name.
I need names of murderers.
I know. Han Daon.
How can a killer become a detective?
Fine, don't tell me. You're mean.
Why won't you believe me?
I've really killed before.
Three people, in fact.
Really?
Yes.
I stabbed them with a knife.
And I can still smell the blood here.
It never goes away.
It might have even gotten more vivid.
How did you become
an officer after killing three people?
Is that possible?
I was young then.
Do you feel bad for the people you killed?
They're already dead.
What's the point of apologizing now?
That's just self-consolation
to ease the guilt.
Did their families forgive you?
They said they never would.
That they'd curse me forever.
They said they hoped
I'd go to Hell when I died.
So...
you're admitting to your crime.
Of course. Not just any crime.
It's deserving of death.
Do you think
I could meet with the families?
You're sitting next to one.
What?
Where?
Detective.
Get up, okay?
You're still here?
I wanted to know
if what you said last night is true.
What did I say last night?
Can you keep it a secret?
So it's true.
Don't worry, your secret's safe with me.
Thank you.
Everyone says I'm not normal
because of the incident.
Despite knowing about that,
you're the first human to look at me,
a demon, without judgement.
And you have convictions
not easily found in other humans.
The conviction
or tenacity
to do what you believe is right,
no matter the cost.
That's why I like you.
And also because you're cute.
Oh, I see.
Either way, thanks.
Sure.
- Your hand.
- What?
I said I'd take you on a walk.
Do you need a treat first?
Uh...
Where do you want to walk?
To Hell.
The Judge from Hell
Gehenna.
You, Justitia, will be punished
for the wrong judgement.
If you object to the punishment,
I will kill you.
Do we know each other?
Justitia?
Can you tell me what happened on this day?
Bring back my son!
Bring me my son back!
My mother-in-law's demanding she
have the death benefit under Jiho's name.
Dad!
No my Jiho. He's my son.
Where's the boy?
He's at an orphanage
because they said I can't raise him.
She abandoned him?
Jiho, are you home?
He's dead.
And bad adults must be punished.
Translated by Jamie Jin